Department of Physics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Physics fonds
1964 - 1991
F-19
2 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Physics
The Department of Physics at S.F.U. was founded in 1964 as a charter department in the Faculty of Science. The Department was responsible, through its Chair, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in the field of Physics. From the outset, the Department has offered programs leading to B.Sc., M.Sc., and Ph.D. degrees. In keeping with the interdisciplinary nature of studies at S.F.U., the Department was involved in co-operative programs within the Faculty of Science, including joint degree programs with Mathematics and Statistics and Chemistry. Since the early 1970s, the Department has been involved in the TRIUMF (Tri-University Meson Facility) project at U.B.C, and it has also been involved in two faculty research bodies: the Theoretical Science Institute and the Energy Research Institute.
The Department was organized administratively into a Chair, Departmental Assistant, Lab Co-ordinator, and a number of standing committees. The Chair was the chief administrative officer, whose responsibilities included the management of the operational budget; faculty tenure, promotion and salary recommendations; teaching assignments; and representation of the Department to external bodies, including the Faculty, Senate and Board of Governors. The Chair reported directly to the Dean of Science. The Departmental Assistant was responsible for much of the day-to-day administration and the management of the departmental budget, the scheduling of courses, the provision of liaison with administrative offices, and advising students. The Lab Co-ordinator acted as liaison between faculty and graduate students and departmental technicians.
The number and composition of departmental committees varied greatly over time. Long-standing committees included Departmental Tenure, Graduate Admissions, Graduate Studies, High School Liaison, Student Qualifying, and Undergraduate Curriculum. There was also departmental representation on faculty and university committees, including the faculty curriculum committees and the University Radiological Safety and University Review committees. The Department also struck ad hoc committees when required.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Department of Physics consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the Department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The records consist chiefly of departmental administrative files (1965-1985), minutes of departmental meetings (1965-1973), records relating to research activities of faculty (1965-1985), personnel records (1965-1985), the Physics Summer School (1966-1979), and correspondence of the Chair (1971-1986). The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curriculum and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include correspondence, course outlines and examinations, an external review, faculty case files, memoranda, agenda and minutes of meetings, and reports.
The files were arranged by the Department according to two different file classification systems. This original order has been maintained. Most of the records are arranged according to the first system, which was therefore used to identify series. Series that can be found in both systems were drawn together intellectually by the archivist and described as one series although their physical order has been maintained as received.
The fonds was arranged and originally described by the archivist in 1992. The arrangement and titles of series by subject were provided by the archivist.
Plischke, Michael; Irwin, J. Chuck; Arrott, Anthony S.; Curzon, Albert E.; Cochrane, John F.; Haering, R. R.
The records were transferred in a number of annual accessions from the Department between 1981 and 1986.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed (as of September 2002: 67 cm., 1968-1991). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory to the Faculty of Science fonds, F-24. Also consult the inventory to the Department of Chemistry fonds, F-6.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Administration - university, 1964 - 1982; F-19-1; 4 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the organization, policies and procedures of the University. It includes memoranda and reports.
  Access may be restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Installation ceremonies (1-01-01), 1964 - 1965; F-19-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
  - President (1-01-02), 1968 - 1975; F-19-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - President (1-01-02), 1976 - 1982; F-19-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Dean, Continuing Studies (1-01-02), 1970 - 1982; F-19-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
- Administration - faculties, 1965 - 1985; F-19-2; 4 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to policy and planning in other departments and faculties that concerned the Department. It includes correspondence and memoranda.
  - Interdisciplinary studies (1-02-02), 1971 - 1984; F-19-2-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Mathematics Department (1-02-03-03), 1968 - 1984; F-19-2-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - University Shops (1-02-03-05), 1965 - 1985; F-19-2-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Computing, Faculty of Science (1-02-03-06-01), 1977; F-19-2-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
- Administration - departmental, 1965 - 1985; F-19-3; 26 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the operations, policies and procedures of the Department. It includes departmental reviews by outside referees; departmental reports, minutes and papers associated with departmental meetings; and memoranda on subjects of importance to the Department.
  - Departmental review (1-03-03), 1972; F-19-3-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Departmental review (1-03-03), 1979; F-19-3-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Report on Physics Department, 1969; F-19-3-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Report on Physics Department, 1970; F-19-3-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-1)
  - Report on Physics Department, 1972; F-19-3-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1965; F-19-3-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1966; F-19-3-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1967; F-19-3-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1968; F-19-3-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1969; F-19-3-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1970; F-19-3-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1971; F-19-3-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1972; F-19-3-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 19-2)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1973; F-19-3-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1974; F-19-3-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1975 - 1976; F-19-3-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1977 - 1978; F-19-3-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1979 - 1980; F-19-3-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1981 - 1982; F-19-3-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Departmental meeting (1-03-04-01), 1983 - 1984; F-19-3-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - University Radiological Safety Committee (1-06-06), 1965 - 1967; F-19-3-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Undergraduate labs (1-03-07), 1971 - 1985; F-19-3-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Eye tests (1-03-08), 1968 - 1969; F-19-3-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Research brochure (1-03-14), 1982; F-19-3-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Research brochure (1-03-14), 1984; F-19-3-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
- Committees, 1968 - 1985; F-19-4; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of university and departmental committees. The documents consist mainly of memoranda to and from the Chair of the Department.
  - Committees - university, 1977 - 1978; F-19-4-1; 2 cm of textual records
    - University Review Committee (1-05-08), 1977; F-19-4-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
    - University Review Committee (1-05-08), 1978; F-19-4-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
    - URC Committee - Reickhoff task force on faculty workloads (1-05-08-01), 1978; F-19-4-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
  - Committees - departmental, 1968 - 1985; F-19-4-2; 2 cm of textual records
    - Departmental committees - general. (1-07-01), 1968 - 1985; F-19-4-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-3)
    - Graduate studies committee (1-07-05)., 1972 - 1974; F-19-4-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
    - Academic discipline, 1981 - 1982; F-19-4-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
- Buildings and services, 1964 - 1985; F-19-5; 3 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to policies and procedures for safety and security in the Physics Department, with particular reference to laboratories. It includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  - Ancillary services- security and safety (2-01-03), 1966 - 1985; F-19-5-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
    Restricted in part
  - Physical plant and planning - general (2-02-01), 1967 - 1985; F-19-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Physical plant and planning - fumehoods (2-02-05), 1981 - 1985; F-19-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Correspondence - Science Complex Building, 1964 - 1968; F-19-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
- Finance - research, 1965 - 1985; F-19-6; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to research activities of members of faculty. It includes correspondence, proposals, and reports.
  - Faculty research reports (3-04-03), 1976 - 1983; F-19-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Reports: PDF and research appointments and non-tenure track visiting scientists (3-04-04), 1967 - 1980; F-19-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Programs of excellence (3-04-06), 1977 - 1979; F-19-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Programs of distinction (3-04-08), 1979 - 1980; F-19-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Programs of distinction (3-04-08), 1981 - 1982; F-19-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Programs of distinction (3-04-08), 1983 - 1984; F-19-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Industrial interaction - Cominco Ltd. (3-04-09-01), 1979 - 1983; F-19-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Industrial interaction - B.C. Hydro (3-04-09-02), 1980 - 1982; F-19-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Industrial interaction - Bell Northern Research (3-04-09-04), 1983 - 1985; F-19-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Industrial interaction - B.C. Telephone Company (3-04-09-06), 1984; F-19-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Industrial interaction - Macdonald, Detwiler and Assoc. Ltd. (3-04-09-07), 1984; F-19-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - Research parks (3-04-16), 1977 - 1985; F-19-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 19-4)
  - MBE System (3-04-14), 1980 - 1982; F-19-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
  - Patents and copyrights (3-04-15), 1965 - 1982; F-19-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
  - EXAF Facility (3-0-16), 1981; F-19-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
- Personnel, 1964 - 1985; F-19-7; 28 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to departmental policy and procedures on appointments. It includes memoranda, policy documents, discussion papers, job descriptions and submissions from the Chair of the Department.
  Access to records in the subseries "Personnel – policy and procedures" and "Personnel – appointment files" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Personnel - policy and procedures, 1966 - 1984; F-19-7-1; 17 cm of textual records
    Access to records in the subseries "Personnel - policy and procedures" and "Personnel - appointment files" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - Appointments, 1966 - 1967; F-19-7-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - University appointments procedures (4-01-03), 1971 - 1982; F-19-7-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - University appointments procedures - faculty authorizations (4-01-03), 1973 - 1983; F-19-7-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Appointment #1 - R, 1972 - 1973; F-19-7-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Appointment report - R, 1973; F-19-7-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Appointment #2 - P, 1975; F-19-7-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - TRIUMF - SFU position (4-01-03-02), 1982; F-19-7-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Search committee - general (4-01-03-04), 1980 - 1982; F-19-7-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Search committee meetings (4-01-03-04), 1975 - 1983; F-19-7-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Sabbatical leave - general (4-01-05), 1966 - 1984; F-19-7-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Faculty consulting - AC31 (4-01-11), 1977 - 1979; F-19-7-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Postdoctoral fellows (4-02-01), 1967 - 1977; F-19-7-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Research associates (4-03-01), 1969 - 1982; F-19-7-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 19-5)
    - Teaching Assistants (4-06-01), 1966 - 1976; F-19-7-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Teaching Assistants (4-06-01), 1977 - 1984; F-19-7-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Sessional instructors (4-07-01), 1978 - 1983; F-19-7-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Job descriptions - technical and secretarial (4-08-06), 1968 - 1982; F-19-7-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Faculy salary review, 1972 - 1973; F-19-7-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
  - Personnel - appointment files, 1964 - 1985; F-19-7-2; 11 cm of textual records
    - Appointments - B, 1981; F-19-7-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
    - Appointments - W, 1969 - 1976; F-19-7-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
    - Appointments - B, 1966 - 1971; F-19-7-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
    - Appointments - D, 1965 - 1973; F-19-7-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
    - Appointments - H, 1964 - 1972; F-19-7-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
    - Appointments - J, 1965 - 1981; F-19-7-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
    - Appointments - J, 1965 - 1981; F-19-7-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
    - Appointments - J, 1965 - 1981; F-19-7-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
    - Appointments - R, 1973 - 1985; F-19-7-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
    - Appointments - V, 1965; F-19-7-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
- Teaching, 1968 - 1985; F-19-8; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to policy on faculty workloads, appointments and evaluation. It includes memoranda, discussion papers, course proposals and records relating to liaison activities.
  Access to records in subseries "Teaching - general" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information
  - Teaching - general, 1972 - 1983; F-19-8-1; 7 cm of textual records
    Access to records in subseries “Teaching - general” is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information
    - Teaching loads (5-01-02), 1975 - 1982; F-19-8-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Teaching appointment applications (5-01-02), #1, 1972 - 1983; F-19-8-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Teaching appointment applications (5-01-02), #2, 1972 - 1983; F-19-8-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Teaching evaluations (5-01-03), 1972 - 1983; F-19-8-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
    - Student opinion surveys (5-01-03-01), F-19-8-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-6)
  - Teaching - secondary, post-secondary, and foreign, 1968 - 1985; F-19-8-2; 4 cm of textual records
    - High school teachers' meetings (5-02-03), 1975; F-19-8-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    - High school demonstration lectures (5-02-04), 1968 - 1984; F-19-8-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    - High school liaison (5-02-10), 1968 - 1985; F-19-8-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    - High school enrichment program (5-02-10-01), 1983 - 1984; F-19-8-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    - Physics articulation meeting (5-02-11), 1979 - 1982; F-19-8-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    - Physics update program (5-02-12), 1981; F-19-8-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    - Proposed Physics course for high school teachers, 1968; F-19-8-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
- Graduate students - course offerings, 1967 - 1983; F-19-9; 3 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to graduate program and course offerings in Physics at S.F.U. It includes course proposals and brochures.
  - Graduate brochures (6-03), 1969 - 1983; F-19-9-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
    Open
  - Curriculum/M.Sc. requirements (6-05), 1973 - 1975; F-19-9-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Graduate course offerings - chemical physics (6-08), 1967 - 1970; F-19-9-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Graduate course proposals (6-08-04), 1974; F-19-9-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - "Irwin proposal" (6-13), 1973; F-19-9-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
- Undergraduate students - course offerings, 1967 - 1985; F-19-10; 9 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to course offerings in the Physics undergraduate program. It includes course proposals and memoranda between the Dean of Science and departmental Chairs.
  - Physics new course proposals (7-04-01), 1969 - 1981; F-19-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Math physics program (7-04-02), 1973 - 1983; F-19-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Computing science program (7-04-03), 1973 - 1983; F-19-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Biophysics program (7-04-04), 1974 - 1983; F-19-10-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Physics lab. 131 (7-04-09), 1974 - 1976; F-19-10-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Special topics course (7-04-10), 1969; F-19-10-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Minor in history and philosophy of science (7-04-13), 1970 - 1972; F-19-10-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Environmental sciences proposal (7-04-14), 1972; F-19-10-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Proposal to modify lower division physics program (7-04-15), 1976; F-19-10-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Physics upper levels revision (7-04-21), 1978; F-19-10-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 19-7)
  - Proposed holography course (7-04-23), 1979 - 1980; F-19-10-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Undergraduate curriculum (7-05), 1967 - 1985; F-19-10-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Grading (7-06), 1974 - 1985; F-19-10-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Course outlines, 1973; F-19-10-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
- Associations and societies, 1974; F-19-11; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the involvement of the Department in external associations and societies, including the Canadian Association of Physicists. The series includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, and registration materials from a symposium held at S.F.U.
  - Canadian Association of Physicists - Symposium at SFU, 1974; F-19-11-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
- Government agencies – Canadian, 1979 - 1985; F-19-12; 3 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to liaison with the government concerning physics instruction. It includes correspondence and associated discussion papers.
  - Universities Council of British Columbia (9-01-06), 1985; F-19-12-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Minister of Education (9-01-09), 1979 - 1984; F-19-12-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Minister of Energy, Mines and Pet. Res. (9-01-10), 1981; F-19-12-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Minister of Science and Technology (9-01-11), 1981 - 1984; F-19-12-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
- Publishing companies, 1970; F-19-13; 1 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to dealings of the Department with publishing companies. It includes correspondence and reports.
  - Physics in Canada (11-03), 1970; F-19-13-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
- Publications, 1966 - 1991; F-19-14; 2 cm of textual records
  Series consists of departmental and university publications to advertise Physics courses, programs, seminars, and conferences. It includes brochures, graduate studies handbooks, and the Physics Students Association newsletter, 1997-1978.
  - Miscellaneous, 1966 - 1983; F-19-14-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Physics Students Association Newsletter, vol. 1 and vol. 2., 1977 - 1978; F-19-14-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
  - Academic programs at SFU, 1990 - 1991; F-19-14-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-8)
- Physics summer school, 1966 - 1975; F-19-15; 30 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the planning and management of advanced summer institutes by the Department of Physics. Participants included graduate students in physics, postdoctoral fellows and senior physicists of international stature. The series includes correspondence, agreements, proceedings, lists of participants, curricula vitae of lecturers and planning documentation.
  - Physics summer school 1967, 1966 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
  - Physics summer school 1967, 1966 - 1971; F-19-15-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
  - Physics summer school 1967, 1967 - 1968; F-19-15-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 19-9)
  - Physics summer school 1968, 1967 - 1968; F-19-15-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1968, 1967 - 1968; F-19-15-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1968, 1967 - 1968; F-19-15-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1968, 1967 - 1968; F-19-15-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1968, 1967 - 1968; F-19-15-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 19-10)
  - Physics summer school 1968, F-19-15-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 19-10)